来る　奴らが必ず来る！
How— Stop. ...did you know? What am I asking that for?
ゴン　キルア　クラピカ レオリオの４人 その約束の朝に ゴンとキルアは ヨークシン市街のマーケットに やって来ていた
The Strong x And x The Weak
えっ？　ここ オークション会場じゃないの？ 決まってんだろ！　ヨークシンの ドリームオークションっていえば
The time has finally come.
数十兆ジェニーの金が動くって いわれてんだ。
At long last...
数十兆ジェニー？ ああ。
Yep.
昨日　１万で競り落とした品物が
The King is about to be born!
闇のオークションも いっぱいあるけどな。
Wait...
すっごいな！
It's too early!
ところで　クラピカとレオリオは 来るかな？
Silence!
レオリオ　サンキュー！ しかし １本　１１万５８０ジェニーか。
I hunger.
新機種だし　あのての店にしちゃ まけてくれたかな。
Bring me food.
ってか　やり過ぎ ケータイ買っただけで
Th-This is our King...
でも　おかげで助かったよ。
Your Majesty!
言っとくが　本気の俺は あんなもんじゃねえ。
O-Oh, no...
相手が　「もう帰ってくれ」って 言ってからが 本当の商談だぜ　君達 ワハハハ…！
Her organs are severely damaged!
何!!　天空闘技場でヒソカに プレートをたたき返した？
Do not make me repeat myself.
それに２００階クラスっていや 相当なもんだぞ！
Bring me food.
どんだけ強くなんだ…。 ねっ　レオリオは 「念」を習得したの？
This is a filthy place...
それは　「纏」っていって 「念」を使いこなすための 四大行の一つ。
You...
え！　「念」って他にもあんの？ そんなことだろうと思った。
Clean this off.
また　何でゲームなんか？ そのゲームには　親父に会うための 手掛かりがあると思うんだ。 えっ？　ゲームに ゴンの親父の手掛かり？
Ah, I happen to have a handkerchief on me—
まっ　話せば長くなるんだけどさ。
Do not make me repeat myself.
それより問題は　値段なんだよ。 いくらだ？ 最低落札希望価格が
I am speaking to you. Clean this off.
お前らの予算じゃ 入場料にも足んねえぜ。
Disgusting.
へっ　やっぱり金だよ 世の中　金　金。
Where is my food?
ってかさ…。 ん？
This way, please.
真の宝とは　いえない ってことだろ？ この程度のものなら 楽勝でゲットしてこそ
We have prepared a meal for you.
プロのハンターなんじゃねえの？ お２人さん。
The three of us will serve
as your arms and legs.
ケッ　んなことは 言われなくても分かってんだよ。
We shall acquire anything you wish...
けどよ　まずは金だ。
And fulfill all of your desires.
ある程度の軍資金がねえと 何にも始まらねえ。 ヨークシンで金を稼ぐ方法を 見つけてやるぜ！
We await your command.
まさかキルの奴 俺を騙したか？
Stop the bleeding!
いや　ない　あいつに ニセゲーを作る技術はないし
Well? How is she?
取引で下手を打つほど バカじゃないだろう
It looks grim... She's in very bad shape.
あいつも騙されて このカードを手に入れたか… 知りたい！　何としても 秘密を暴いてやる！
Multiple organs have been crushed
so badly, we cannot heal them!
いくら払ってでも！
If something isn't done...
確実に競り落とすには　倍は 用意しておきたいとこだな
Neferpitou-dono!
親父　取引だ。
The Queen is dying...
１５人殺るから １５０億　貸してくれ。
We require your assistance!
ああ　うん　じゃ。
We need the power you
used to heal that man!
１０歳ぐらいだったかな。 最後に外出したのって…。
I only healed him because I need him.
あっ？　「交わし」？ 何だろう　「交わし」って。
Now that the King has been born, she means nothing to the Royal Guard.
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]　「交わし」　競売方法の一つ 物々交換の俗称。 他にも　「縛り」などがある。
She is no longer necessary.
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]　「縛り」　売り手側が金品以外の ある条件を示し
Your Majesty!
その条件に最も適した 買い手に対して
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
条件？ 何のこっちゃ。
Well? Will Neferpitou-dono help us?
イヒヒ…　そうか。
No, Neferpitou-dono has...
こんな競売のやり方が あったのか…　イヒヒヒ。
No... They have all abandoned the Queen. Abandoned?
今夜　午後９時
We'll have to save the Queen ourselves!
地下競売でコルコ王女のミイラが 競売にかけられる。
It's impossible! Weren't you listening to me?
イワレンコフ トチーノ　ヴェーゼ 競りは　お前達に任せる。
We don't have the power to heal the damage the Queen has suffered...
３人で大丈夫なのか？ 買人側は ３人１組でしか入れないし
Perhaps they have the power we need. Who are you talking about?
武器　記録装置 通信機器の携帯も許されない。
Hey, where are you going?
マフィアンコミュニティーが 全責任を持って　行っている。 それゆえ 問題は　ほとんど起きていない。
We have prepared your dinner on the roof,
where there is a fine view.
下手すりゃ　全世界のマフィアを 敵に回すことになるからな。
Then, it would seem faster
to get there from outside.
だから　コミュニティー側も 防犯ビデオなどは使っていない。
Magnificent...
仲間以外との会話も慎め。
Excuse me.
競売品は　こちら ３００万相当のダイヤ！ その店で買ったばかりの 鑑定書付きだぜ！
It seems I need practice.
はいはい　押さないで 順番よ！
Disgusting. You don't like it?
((相手の力具合を見て 手加減すること))
It is horrendously bland.
)
We haven't been seasoning our food... No, that is not what I mean.
はい　では　あなたから 参加費用は前払いだよ。 ほらよ　１万ジェニー。 まいど　では　どうぞ！
When I was in her belly, I was occasionally treated to
wonderfully rich, savory meals.
では　手を握って…。
Ah, you must be talking
about the rare humans.
俺の言った通りにやれよ うん
My body longs for that
indescribable satisfaction.
ようござんすか？ １本勝負ですぜ。
I wish to feast upon one of them.
レディー　ゴー！
As you wish.
フン！ フン！　んん…　ん！
In that case...
もうちょっとだ　さぁ　頑張れ！
One of them is heading straight for us.
んん…　ん！
Have we been seen?
あっ　あぁ…。
Let's hide...
ん…　　おぉ！
Wait. Something seems off...
んん…　んぐ…　ぐっ…！
Look!
ん…。 あぁ…。 あ　残念。
A white flag?
では次の人　どうぞ！ レディー　ゴー！
We surrender!
こういうのが条件競売か…
でも　最低８９億　稼ぐまで
But there is one condition...
あと８８万９９９９勝…
You must save the Queen!
クソ！ はい　負け！　次の人　どうぞ。
She no longer has the ability to give birth. The Queen? The King has already been born!
はい　負け！ おぉ！
Impossible! It's too early!
何だか騙してるみたいで 気が引けるな
He is...
こんな楽して お金もうけなんて… おかげで 冷や汗まで　かいちゃった…
They are all
さて　次の人　どうぞ…　おっ？
devils...
ん…　ぐっ…　うっ…。
What is this?
くっ…　うっ…　んん…！
They put up no fight.
ん…　んん…。
Disgusting.
ん…　ぐっ…　ん…。
This is all wrong. Might I offer some advice?
ん…。 あっ…。
The brain is the most delicious part of a human.
はい　残念　負けちゃった！ よくやった　ねえちゃん！
So I'd recommend dispatching your
prey without harming the head.
ありがとうございました。 あっ　どういたしまして。
Is that so?
腕相撲の 世界チャンピオンじゃねえ？
Like this? Magnificent!
そうね　なぜ利き腕で やらなかったか？ あっ　そうか 相手が右手　出したから　つい…。
I see... This is not so bad. However...
もう一回　挑戦したいな。 ダメよ　もう時間ね 仕事開始よ。
It is still inedible,
when compared to a rare human.
そうそう　それに 買ったり競ったりは邪道だぜ。
Might I offer more advice?
俺達　盗賊。 欲しいものは奪い取るね。
There is a way to identify rare humans. If you use—
ヤダ！　絶対行くの！ う!!
Do you insult me?
[TEL]　聞こえますか？ お手上げです！
I am aware that if I focus, I can see the
energy around their bodies.
はい。 今は暴れ… 泣き疲れて寝ていますが
Haven't we already lost our reason to stay?
起きた時には どうなるか分かりませんよ。
The Queen can no longer reproduce. Huh?
もちろん　お嬢様が望んでいる アイテムは必ず入手しますが
That's true.
今回は　お嬢様の目的は 自分で　お宝を競り落とすこと。
It's no longer possible for the
Queen to build her kingdom.
ですから
In that case, each of us should
try to become a king...
目覚めて　競売に参加 できなかったことを知ったら どれだけ失望することか。
We can do as we please.
[TEL]　分かった　俺も予定を 繰り上げて　そちらに向かう。
Do you realize what you're saying?
[TEL]　とにかく　まず　「王女のミイラ」を 確実に手に入れて ネオンの機嫌をとっておけ。 分かりました。
You think you can get away with this? I'm sure we aren't the only ones
who'd like to leave this place.
外からは変化なし。 了解　何かあったら連絡を入れる。
W-Wait...
でも　徹底してるわね。 コミュニティー専属の 警備員以外は 会場の半径５００ｍ以内に 近づくこともできないってのは。
Now do you see that you're in the minority?
そうしないと　あの周り中が
Please... There's no time!
こわもてだらけに なってしまうからだろう。
If the Queen dies, there will be nothing to hold
the Squadron Leaders back.
「ここで悪事が行われてますよ」と 宣伝するようなものだからな。
Things will spin out of control. What exactly will happen then?
まぁね。
Most likely, they will imitate the King.
本当に現れるのか？ 「幻影旅団」は…
They will leave to build their own
kingdoms by spreading their seed.
ん？
If the chain of command collapses, some of the Captains will also strike out alone.
あの時の音と同じね。 ん？ 実は　私
They will scatter throughout the world
and destroy entire ecosystems. Are Chimera Ant soldiers
capable of reproduction?
あなたがハンターの斡旋所から 出て来るのを見たのよ。
Yes... They can copulate with females
of other species and reproduce.
あの時の　あなたの心音は
Soldiers belonging to a colony led by a queen
すさまじい怒りの旋律だった。
will not attempt to reproduce. But I've read reports
一つ　聞いていいかしら？ ああ。 緋の目。
of soldiers attempting to reproduce
following a queen's death.
…って　あなたにとって何？
Well, I'd say we can safely assume he isn't lying.
聞いてどうする？
What's your name?
別に　どうもしないけど　好奇心よ。 データカードで　その画像を 見せられた時の　あなたの心音は
Colt. Colt, we're going to take you to our boss.
さらに　すさまじかったもの。
I need you to tell your story to him directly.
底知れぬ　深い怒りの旋律。
However, I don't know if he will trust you.
ウソは　通用しそうにないな。
And even if he believes your story, he may not let you leave alive.
私は　クルタ族だ。 我々の瞳は普段　茶に近いが
Are you still willing to come with us? Absolutely! Time is of the essence!
そこで悟られぬように 黒のコンタクトをしている。
The timing couldn't be worse.
私は同胞の 奪われた目を捜している。
Today is the day our disciples fight it out...
仲間の元へ… どんなことをしても取り戻す。
Oh! I completely forgot... I bet 100,000 that Knuckle
and Shoot would make it.
ふん。 ダルツォルネに報告するか？
You bet 1,000,000 that all five would come...
「話すなら恨みはないが 仕方がない」って音がしてた。
Knuckle... Huh?
聞いてどうするの？ どうせデタラメ言うかもよ。
Promise me!
目を見れば　大体分かる。
You have to... You have to save Kite!
フッ…。
Got it...
私もプロのハンターよ。
I promise I'll bring him back.
ミュージックハンター というところかしら。
Rook I swear on this token.
恐ろしい災いが 降りかかるとされている。
Killua...
怪談の類いではないのか？ そんなものが実在するとは 考えにくいが…。
I'm weak...
あっ…。
I never knew...
その人も知人から 「絶対に吹かない」との条件で
I never knew
１楽章だけを 教えてもらったらしいけど…。
how frustrating
その日　私達は 酔って浮かれてたの。
weakness could be!
だね。
For the thirty days that you can't use Nen...
ついに牙をむく「幻影旅団」
I'll protect you.
ノストラードファミリーのボディーガードとして 雇われているクラピカは 彼らに　どう立ち向かうのか？
I will do whatever it takes!